So, I'm really interested.
所以我真的很感兴趣
It's what I call bridging the gap between the poets and the quants,
这就是我所说的弥合诗人和量化人之间的鸿沟,
and the idea is to make numbers tell a story and speak to people who are not necessarily
这个想法就是让数字讲述一个故事 并且告诉那些不一定
accustomed to working with data to make
习惯于处理数据
it into a story that they can digest understand and then act upon.
他们可以消化理解 然后采取行动
So, I started out as a literary agent and studied
所以 我开始作为一个文稿代理人和研究
English literature and I realized that I
英国文学和我意识到我
was actually interested in transitioning to the business side of media.
真的有兴趣转向媒体的商业领域
So, during my MBA,
所以在我读 MBA 的时候,
I focused on statistics and big data electives wherever I could and I also
我尽可能地专注于统计学和大数据选修课
pursued my own online learning to learn the coding bits and the technical bit.
追求我自己的在线学习编码位和技术位
Just after the MBA joined the Bertlesmann group in the Bertlesmann entrepreneurs program.
就在 MBA 毕业后不久 贝尔特莱斯曼集团加入了贝尔特莱斯曼企业家项目
In terms of the music industry at large,
就整个音乐产业而言,
the main applications of data science are around streaming.
数据科学的主要应用是流媒体
So, how do people discover music,
那么 人们是如何发现音乐的,
how are they consuming music especially being able to track
他们是如何消费音乐 特别是能够跟踪
the path from discovery to becoming a fan on streaming services.
从发现到成为流媒体服务粉丝的道路
Finding new acts, how can you automate some of that search especially given the explosion
寻找新的行为 你如何自动化的搜索 特别是在爆炸
of just the amount of content that is out
内容的数量
there also just around being able to forecast and predict.
还有就是能够预测和预测
Sales, how much stock you should hold a final and CDs for example,
销售额 你应该持有多少存货 例如期末和 cd,
for me it was really an experience of realizing
对我来说 这是一次真正意识到
that you can teach yourself a tremendous amount of skills
你可以自学大量的技能
and especially technical skills and I as somebody who
尤其是技术能力 而我作为一个
originally was maybe afraid of things like coding,
最初可能害怕编码之类的东西,
was able to just with persistence teach myself
能够坚持不懈地教会我自己
something and I feel like that's something that can really
我觉得这些东西真的可以
scale because if I can do it really anybody can.
因为如果我能做到 任何人都能做到 .最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6